{
    "id": "6f654877af114a52b16c2c1d5f5a40e3",
    "title": "Conjunctions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e2a5bdd914be4767a6da359e219d968f",
            "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I waited for him …………………. 7 o’clock and then I went home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "till",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will make a cake ………………… I have time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "when",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They had left ………………… the time I reached their place.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "before",
                        "when"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. the teacher left the classroom, the students started chatting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As soon as",
                        "No sooner",
                        "Hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will call you ……………….. I leave.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "till",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Take this bag with you …………………. you leave.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "after",
                        "before",
                        "when"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was depressed ………………….. she didn’t know what to do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "because",
                        "because of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We must reach there ………………… he leaves.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "until",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I cut myself …………………. I was shaving.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "whenever",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We cancelled the trip ………………… it was raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "because",
                        "in case",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}